tungle.me 2011-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Tungle.me | Scheduling Made Easy

2254772 Ontario Inc. (“TUNGLE”) is committed to your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information from our customers (“Users”), as well as from visitors to our site and potential customers (“Visitors”) who have communicated with us about our products and services. Rest assured that except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, TUNGLE will never trade, sell, or rent to any third party the identifiable information that you provide to us without your consent. TUNGLE complies with all laws and regulations to which it is subject with regard to the use and disclosure of your information.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding TUNGLE’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at contact [support@tungle.com.](mailto:support@tungle.com)

## Collecting Personal Information

### Information we collect about you

In order to provide and market our products and services to our Users, TUNGLE collects personally identifiable information when you register with us. This includes but is not limited to your name, email address, certain user names and passwords depending on the calendaring platform that you use, credit card information (where applicable) and other personal information (collectively, “Identifiable Information”). TUNGLE may also collect photos, contact information, links to sites that you own, etc (collectively Your “Content”). Finally, TUNGLE may also collect Identifiable Information from Visitors when they communicate with us about our services and products or during other transactions or interactions.

### Information we collect

TUNGLE may also collect non-personally identifiable information when you use our services or our Internet site (“Non-Identifiable Information”). Non-Identifiable Information may include web site pages viewed, Usage Information (see below), demographic data, cookies and other information which does not specifically identify any one individual.

### Automatic collection

To make your visits more convenient and to enable us to enhance our services, TUNGLE may use cookies to customize your visit to our Internet sites and for other purposes.

“Cookies” are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing communication and interaction with that web site. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes.

In addition to cookies, TUNGLE may also use (and TUNGLE’s third party advertisers may use) clear gifs, web beacons and third party cookies to improve the performance of our Internet sites, provide certain features such as advertising or to anonymously track usage of our Internet sites and track the online activity on our sites. TUNGLE also may use such devices in our htm-based emails to track the usage of these emails.

You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer, including third party cookies, or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. In this case, you may still use TUNGLE’s web site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality.

### No Spyware

TUNGLE believes that Spyware is a threat to your privacy and your experience online. That’s why TUNGLE forbids any employee, agent, partner, affiliate or contractor from intentionally deploying or using Spyware (as defined in this policy) on behalf of TUNGLE. Spyware refers to any executable software application that is installed on a user’s personal computer and covertly gathers and transmits Identifiable Information through the user’s Internet connection without the knowledge or consent of the user. Cookies and web beacons are not considered Spyware. Spyware may gather Identifiable Information, such as e-mail addresses and credit card information, and may even alter personal computer settings. Intentional use of Spyware by any TUNGLE employee, agent, partner or affiliate on TUNGLE’s behalf will not be tolerated and will be considered grounds for dismissal and contract termination.

## How we use this information

### Identifiable information

TUNGLE will use Identifiable Information (1) to market products and services that we believe may be of interest to you, (2) to provide services and products requested by you, and (3) to enable its vendors and contractors to provide and assist TUNGLE in the marketing and provision of such services and products to you. However, TUNGLE will not share your credit card information with any third parties unless they are involved in processing payments for services that you have purchased from TUNGLE. TUNGLE only works with partners whom TUNGLE believes maintain high standards with respect to privacy and consumer rights.

TUNGLE may also use and disclose Identifiable Information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activities that threaten the integrity of our service or network, to investigate fraud or violations of our Terms of Service, as required by courts or administrative agencies or in connection with a sale, merger or reorganization of TUNGLE’s business.

Non-Identifiable Information may be shared with any number of third parties by TUNGLE.

### Usage Information

In the course of providing services to you, TUNGLE collects and maintains certain customer service usage information (“Usage Information”). Usage Information includes, for example, meetings booked, contacts imported, sharing requests sent, calendar platform that you use (i.e. Outlook vs. Google, etc) etc and other potential usage and billing information for those services. Generally, TUNGLE can use Users’ Usage Information to offer you additional services, and for billing and collections purposes.

We value our relationships with our Users and are committed to respecting and protecting your Usage Information. Accordingly, TUNGLE does not sell, trade or share your Usage Information, including usage records outside of TUNGLE’s systems, except as authorized by you or required by law. TUNGLE can also disclose Users’ Usage Information for legal or regulatory reasons, including in response to subpoenas and court orders. TUNGLE can also use Usage Information to investigate fraud and to prevent violation of our Terms of Service and unlawful use of our network, services and other Users.

## Keeping your information secure

TUNGLE has invested and deployed a wide variety of technology and security features to make reasonable efforts to ensure the privacy of information on our network. In addition, TUNGLE has implemented operations guidelines to ensure your privacy is safeguarded at every level of our organization. TUNGLE will continue to revise policies and implement additional security features as new technologies becomes available. However, no system or service can give a 100% guaranty of security, especially a service that relies upon the public Internet. Therefore, Users acknowledge the risk that third parties may gain unauthorized access to your information when using TUNGLE’s services.

## Communications

TUNGLE will not read, or disclose to any third parties, private e-mail or other communications that are transmitted using TUNGLE services except as required to ensure proper operation of services or as otherwise authorized by law.

Users should be aware that any Identifiable Information which you voluntarily include and transmit through publicly accessible forums (i.e., such as chat rooms, blogs, instant messages, listservs) may be viewed and used by anyone with access to such forums. TUNGLE is unable to control such uses of your Identifiable Information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the Identifiable Information provided by them may be viewed and used by third parties.

## Account Information

Subject to certain security requirements, TUNGLE will do its best to honor requests from Users for account information, for example, name, address, company, or billing information. The Member is responsible for ensuring that the information on file with TUNGLE is current and accurate.

## Children’s Privacy Policy

TUNGLE does not sell products or services for purchase by children. TUNGLE does not knowingly solicit or collect Identifiable Information from children or teenagers under the age of eighteen. If a User believes that a minor has disclosed Identifiable Information to TUNGLE, the Member should contact [support@tungle.com.](mailto:support@tungle.com) to report this to TUNGLE.

## TUNGLE Spam Policy

TUNGLE has zero tolerance for spam. Spam complaints will be dealt with seriously and can result in losing TUNGLE services and privileges.

## Third Party Web Sites and Services

TUNGLE’s service may contain links to other Internet-based resources and services not maintained by TUNGLE. In addition, other web sites and services may also reference or link to TUNGLE. TUNGLE encourages its Users to be aware when you leave TUNGLE’s service or surf the Internet, and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site and service that you visit. TUNGLE does not endorse, screen or approve, and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of, such other web sites and services.

TUNGLE does not assume any liability for third parties that have been provided with information as permitted by this Privacy Policy or who have collected information as permitted by this Privacy Policy (such as advertisers using third party cookies).

### If you want to Opt Out

As a Member, if you do not want any of your Identifiable Information used by TUNGLE for any direct marketing purposes, then you may opt-out of such disclosures by e-mailing TUNGLE at [support@tungle.com.](mailto:support@tungle.com).

However, TUNGLE is not responsible for removing User’s Identifiable Information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided such information in accordance with this policy and your prior consent. Since TUNGLE must use a your Identifiable Information in order to provide you with TUNGLE services, you cannot opt-out of all uses of their Identifiable Information unless you cancel your service.

## Changes to privacy policy

TUNGLE reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time by posting such changes here. Users should review this policy regularly for changes, and can easily see if changes have been made by checking the Effective Date below. However, if at any time in the future TUNGLE plans to use Identifiable Information in a way that differs from this policy, TUNGLE will post such changes here and provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use following the posting of any changes to this policy means acceptance of such changes.

## Terms of Service

For Users, this Privacy Policy is subject to the TUNGLE Terms of Service or other agreements between Users and TUNGLE. You should refer to the Terms of Service or such other agreements regarding certain rights and limitations with respect to your use of TUNGLE’s services.

## Change of Control

If the ownership of all or substantially all of TUNGLE were to change, your Usership information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy.

## Disclaimer

Copyright © Tungle Corporation. All Rights Reserved. The materials on these web pages are copyrighted by Tungle Corporation. Tungle PROVIDES THE INFORMATION ON THESE WEB PAGES AS IS AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES. Tungle DISCLAIMS ALL EXPRESS AND IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IN NO EVENT WILL TUNGLE BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS, USE, OR DATA OR FOR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER SORT. Tungle may make changes to the web page materials and the product information and prices at any time without notice and without obligation to update the materials contained on these web pages.

## Questions

For common questions and answers regarding TUNGLE’s privacy policy or to contact TUNGLE, contact [support@tungle.com.](mailto:support@tungle.com).

## Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was last updated on November 24, 2009.
